Come clean and admit your crime,
you failure.
What a barbaric, boring conclusion.
Did you think a delicate girl like me
would face a barbaric man like you alone?
I was hoping Ram was
mistaken about all this.
Tell me... What happened, Subaru?
Why did all this...
I-It was—
Maybe he'll feel up to talking
if we give him a little pain.
Wait!
We were going to talk to Subaru
because he was acting strange!
Wasn't that the plan?
You are too soft, Lady Emilia.
Remember the Sin Archbishop
who could take others' forms?
Isn't it possible that Sin
Archbishop has taken Barusu's form?
Well...
I'll make him talk right now.
He'll tell us where the
real Barusu and Meili are.
They weren't the ones who moved Meili?
Ram, please, stop this!
You can't just decide
whether he's real or not!
I lost my memories!
After all this... What kind of joke is that?!
Ram!
You heard Subaru! There must be a reason!
And Rem?
What happens to Rem?
Stay out of my way!
Tell me again that you forgot.
No... That's not...
Tell me one more time, with that
face and voice, that you forgot Rem.
Don't, Ram!
Ow...
The cage...
Where are Emilia and Ram?
Subaru Natsuki Was Here
Huh?
The hell is with this creepy-ass room?
Why would you decorate a room
with nasty shit like this,
bro?
Hah! The hell's with that face, bro?
You chicken or what?
You look like you're gonna cry.
You get into a fight with your buddies?
That's funny.
W-Wait! You...
You said you couldn't come down
from the floor above here!
Your assumption fell apart, that's all.
My assumption fell apart? Why—
Ow!
Dumbass. Don't go thinkin' you'll
get answers to everything.
I can walk around.
So I'm goin' outside.
Outside? Outside the tower?
Just gotta clean up one little regret.
Regret?
Wait, what about the exam, then?!
Aw, hell. Here he comes.
I don't see your other buddies.
Well, that just makes
this easier, I guess.
This is the perfect chance
to get that guy killed!
Now you'll get to read
another book of the dead!
Behind you, Julius!
Hah! Weaklings don't have a lot of options!
All they ever get good at is making excuses.
Why are you here?
Why? What? How?
You're asking the same questions
he did. You bosom buddies?
Come on! Come on! Come on! Come on!
Now, back to the exam.
Try to rip this outta my hands
before I get bored, bro.
Echidna...
Take care of Echidna and Lady Anastasia!
Hah!
That disposition of yours
really never changes, huh?
Where do you think you're going?
Why'd you help that guy, anyway?
After you wrung my neck, even.
Subaru!
I've been looking for you!
You shouldn't go that way, I suppose!
Why are you outside the cage?
Beatrice, get away from him!
Ram told me he isn't the Natsuki you know!
Ram?
That's right.
I didn't kill Emilia and Ram.
That's not true!
Once I hold his hand,
I'll know, I suppose!
Still, we can't trust him.
I should've just obeyed
Ana's gut instinct.
I never should have
brought anyone else here.
This is my failure.
So what? That doesn't even matter!
This tower's done for!
What's wrong with you, Subaru?
It isn't like you to talk
like that, I suppose!
And what is "like me"?!
Where is the "me" that you guys see?!
You're still sticking to the pathetic
lie that you lost your memories?
Ram's forgotten her sister,
and Julius has been forgotten by everyone,
and you still continue this cruel act?
Act? You think this is an act?!
You're saying what I'm doing
now is an act?!
If I could act, don't you think I'd
act out something better than this?!
Who the hell would want
to become Subaru Natsuki?!
A disgusting creep like this?!
None of you know anything!
Who am I?!
I lost everything!
I was going home
from the convenience store!
I didn't talk to anyone all day
other than the clerk there!
And then, suddenly, another world?
A tower in the sand? Corpses?!
Exams?! Fakes?! Subaru Natsuki?!
Screw you!
Screw you all!
I bet you're wondering why I
just suddenly lost my shit, huh?
Well, I just suddenly hit my limit!
Something in me just snapped!
I can't do anything, even if I want to!
So...
So... please forgive me.
Please forgive me.
Just let me go home already.
If God's trying to punish
me for something, I get it.
I was wrong!
Subaru...
Beatrice, go with him.
I'll look for Julius.
Understood.
Come on, Subaru. For now, just—
And what's the meaning of this?
I considered that a compromise.
So why are you doing this?
Julius asked me to.
He did?
Incomplete E-M-T, I suppose!
Natsuki... Please don't do
such unpredictable things.
Like I could help it!
It was a spur-of-the-moment thing!
El Jiwaldo!
Just what are you?
What do you hope to accomplish?
Whose side are you on?
I don't know, either.
Because I...
Lost your memories.
You don't even remember when you took
Betty out of the mansion, I suppose?
Sorry...
I...
It's fine.
You may have forgotten it,
but Betty never will.
I'll always remember.
Let's move. We can't stay here.
Echidna, you...
I still have my misgivings about you.
But right now, I have to prioritize.
It's a necessary mindset for any merchant.
I've been seeing that
up close for a long time.
All right.
Enough.
Just... leave me.
Damn it... Damn it, damn it, damn it!
Natsuki...
You've... done enough...
Like hell I have!
Nothing I've done has been enough!
Shouldn't Beatrice... come before me?
I see.
She was truly... an unfortunate girl.
It hurts.
Oh, how it hurts.
Human bodies are so painful.
Sorry...
Sorry!
It's not... I didn't mean to...
I—
This pain...
is the only way I can repay Ana.
I mean, isn't it?
If I were to return her body to her now...
she'd have to feel this pain...
and this fear of death.
Don't feel like... you have
to make it easier for me.
This... is fine with me.
Hey, did you hear that?
Isn't this what they call a windfall?
It's all right, Big Brother.
You're just putting her out of her misery.
You can't even do something
that simple, Subaru Natsuki?
Natsuki...
You can't even lift a rock
to put me out of my misery.
Sorry... for doubting you.
Why don't you just die?
Yeah...
I love you.
Stop it! I'm sick of this!
I don't!
I don't... love me!
I knew I was loved.
I knew it!
My mom and dad loved me from
the bottom of their hearts.
I knew it! How the hell could I not?!
That's why... I wished
I could just disappear.
My parents loved me so much,
but I could never love someone
like me who wasn't worth loving!
I love you.
Stop it!
I love you. I love you. I love you.
Give me a break! Isn't this enough?!
I already knew the answer ages ago!
The people who tried so desperately...
with all they had...
to be nice to me
could never be bad people!
I knew that!
That's why I should have died.
If this can be the end of it...
If Subaru Natsuki can just
disappear, and that'll end it...
I love you. I love you. I love you.
That's enough!
Subaru!
Enough.
Huh?
I've had enough!
Why are you trying to help me?
Subaru...
Something's wrong with you!
You and Julius and Beatrice!
Even Echidna was apologizing
to me in the end!
It makes no sense!
Echidna... in the end?
Subaru, what happened?
Where are Echidna and—
They're dead!
Her legs blew off!
She was hurt so bad.
She lost so much blood...
Same with Beatrice!
And Julius... "Go," he said...
"Take care of them," he said...
What an idiot.
They're all idiots.
What do they expect of me?
"Take care of them"?
"Get her back"?
"Sorry I doubted you"?
What are you talking about?
You and I first met at a place in
the capital called the loot house.
Huh?
At the time, Felt had stolen my insignia,
something very important to me.
Puck and I were panicking
about how to get it back.
Then after chasing Felt down,
I became a target
for Meili's older sister...
and you saved my life.
That's how you and I first met.
Do you remember?
But you were badly hurt protecting me,
so I took you back to
Roswaal's mansion with me.
Beatrice healed you there, though
she complained all the while.
Then Ram... and Rem, too, I'm sure...
became your friends.
And then Meili, rather than her sister,
sent mabeasts to do evil things to us.
You and Ram stopped her,
Roswaal took care of the mabeasts,
and I just stayed home.
That was when we promised
to go on a "date," too.
Do you remember?
Then I was called to the capital
for the royal selection, and...
that was the first time you
and I had a really big fight.
I didn't want you to be reckless
and get yourself hurt again,
and I didn't understand why
you were so kind to me.
I was scared.
So when we fought, I was
sure it was all over, but...
When I didn't know what was happening
and I was being swept away in a
situation that didn't feel right,
you rushed to my rescue... and...
Do you remember what you said to me then?
But I remember all of it.
Everything you said for me, did for me,
and promised you'd do for me.
I remember all of it.
I don't remember!
I can't remember!
You...
You... All of you...
Who the hell are you talking about?!
Someone who can risk his life for others?!
Someone who can take
action in a heartbeat?!
Someone who can take off
running to help others?!
Someone who can put his own life
on the line to accomplish things?!
Get real!
Someone like that can't be Subaru Natsuki!
I know just how pathetic and
useless Subaru Natsuki is!
I know he's a good-for-nothing
scumbag who's rotten to the core!
Subaru Natsuki is a good-for-nothing
I know that better than anyone!
Why should it have to be me?
Someone much stronger or
smarter can do it.
But I... I can't do it. I can't.
My name is Emilia.
Just Emilia.
There are so many things
I need to tell you,
and things I need to ask you.
But right now, just tell me one thing.
Please... tell me your name.
Why?
Why must it be Subaru Natsuki now?
What can he even do?
What do you expect from him?!
You might be right.
There are people who
are stronger than you,
and plenty who are smarter, too, I'm sure.
But... no matter what happens,
you're the one I want to be with.
I hope and believe that
that's what you'll do.
Because...
Because if someone's going to help me,
rather than someone who does it because
they can, or because they're there...
I'd be much, much happier
if it's someone I love.
Oh...
Subaru Natsuki...
You were in love with
a beautiful girl like this?
And that was the source
of your strength, huh?
Could she be any more out of your league?
How do you get to aim so high?
How does a loser like you end
up with a beauty like her?
My name is Emilia.
Just Emilia.
Please...
tell me your name.
My name is Subaru Natsuki.
The man Julius trusted,
Beatrice believed in,
Echidna forgave...
and you, Emilia, hope for...
If his name is Subaru Natsuki...
then I'm Subaru Natsuki.
I want to help them.
I want to save them from this tower.
If Subaru Natsuki can do that,
I'm going to do it.
Thank you for letting
me believe that, Emilia.
Subaru,
I—
Emilia!
Subaru!
Is this gonna end with us
getting swallowed up in that?
No. This is not the end.
This... This is gonna be where it begins!
I'll remember.
I'll remember everything!
Even if you forget me...
Re:ZERO -Starting Life in Another World-
I'll never forget any of you!
Subaru!
Hey, Subaru!
Are you all right?
Oh, what a relief!
I was so worried about you!
Emilia, you need to be firmer or he...
I'm back.